<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>JBake</title>
    <link>http://rmchale.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://rmchale.github.io//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>JBake Bootstrap Template</description>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2015 17:34:41 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2015 17:34:41 -0600</lastBuildDate>

    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Ergonomic Sculpt Mouse on the Mac</title>
      <link>http://rmchale.github.io//blog/2015/sculpt-mouse.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2015 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">blog/2015/sculpt-mouse.html</guid>
      <description>
      &lt;div style=&quot;text-align:center&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;images/sculpt-mouse.jpg&quot; width=&quot;500&quot;&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h3&gt;OVERVIEW&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I want to map the mouse keys on my Microsoft Ergonomic Sculpt mouse that came with my new &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/Microsoft-Sculpt-Ergonomic-Desktop-L5V-00001/dp/B00CYX54C0/&quot;&gt;Microsoft Sculpt Erconomic Keyboard&lt;/a&gt;. Its a bit of an odd duck of a mouse. It is oddly shaped and a bit uncormforable to use. It is however less uncomfortable than my &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/Apple-MB829Z-A-Magic-Mouse/dp/B002NX0M8C&quot;&gt;Apple Magic Mouse&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The main problem I have is that the Windows key does not work with on my Mac. I have found &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.yorkxin.org/posts/2014/04/12/microsoft-sculpt-mobile-mouse-and-mac/&quot;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt; blog post discussing how to fix it. Per the instructions I installed &lt;a href=&quot;https://pqrs.org/osx/karabiner/index.html.en&quot;&gt;Karabiner&lt;/a&gt; and after a little tinkering was able to map the Windows key to mouse button #5.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From there I used &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.boastr.net/&quot;&gt;bettertouchtool&lt;/a&gt; to map both the thumb buttons to Expose and Mission Control switcher. Below is the private.xml I used in Karabiner. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The mouse is still a tad uncomfortable, but so far so good in terms of mapping the mouse buttons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;PRIVATE.xml&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;xml&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;root&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;deviceproductdef&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;productname&amp;gt;SCULPT_ERGONOMIC&amp;lt;/productname&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;productid&amp;gt;0x07a5&amp;lt;/productid&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/deviceproductdef&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;item&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;name&amp;gt;Windows Button to Mission Control (Microsoft Sculpt Ergonomic Mouse)&amp;lt;/name&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;identifier&amp;gt;com.microsoft.mouse.sculpt_mobile.win_button&amp;lt;/identifier&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;device_only&amp;gt;DeviceVendor::MICROSOFT,DeviceProduct::SCULPT_ERGONOMIC&amp;lt;/device_only&amp;gt;
    &amp;lt;autogen&amp;gt;
      __KeyToKey__
      KeyCode::OPTION_R,
      KeyCode::VK_MOUSEKEY_BUTTON_BUTTON5
    &amp;lt;/autogen&amp;gt;
  &amp;lt;/item&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/root&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Links&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://pqrs.org/osx/karabiner/index.html.en&quot;&gt;Karabiner&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.yorkxin.org/posts/2014/04/12/microsoft-sculpt-mobile-mouse-and-mac/&quot;&gt;Instructions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/osx/comments/2vozkq/anyone_use_the_ms_sculpt_comfort_mouse_on_latest/&quot;&gt;Reddit&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>There's Always Next Year / Casey at the Bat</title>
      <link>http://rmchale.github.io//blog/2015/casey-at-the-bat.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">blog/2015/casey-at-the-bat.html</guid>
      <description>
      &lt;p&gt;It&apos;s been a while since I posted this. Usually its for my Red Sox. But I think its time I post it for my adopted city and the Cubbies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;The outlook wasn&apos;t brilliant for the Mudville nine that day;&lt;br/&gt;The score stood four to two, with but one inning more to play,&lt;br/&gt;And then when Cooney died at first, and Barrows did the same,&lt;br/&gt;A pall-like silence fell upon the patrons of the game. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A straggling few got up to go in deep despair. The rest&lt;br/&gt;Clung to that hope which springs eternal in the human breast;&lt;br/&gt;They thought, &apos;If only Casey could but get a whack at that-&lt;br/&gt;We&apos;d put up even money now, with Casey at the bat.&apos; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Flynn preceded Casey, as did also Jimmy Blake,&lt;br/&gt;And the former was a hoodoo, while the latter was a cake;&lt;br/&gt;So upon that stricken multitude grim melancholy sat,&lt;br/&gt;For there seemed but little chance of Casey getting to the bat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Flynn let drive a single, to the wonderment of all,&lt;br/&gt;And Blake, the much despisèd, tore the cover off the ball;&lt;br/&gt;And when the dust had lifted, and men saw what had occurred,&lt;br/&gt;There was Jimmy safe at second and Flynn a-hugging third. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then from five thousand throats and more there rose a lusty yell;&lt;br/&gt;It rumbled through the valley, it rattled in the dell;&lt;br/&gt;It pounded on the mountain and recoiled upon the flat,&lt;br/&gt;For Casey, mighty Casey, was advancing to the bat. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was ease in Casey&apos;s manner as he stepped into his place;&lt;br/&gt;There was pride in Casey&apos;s bearing and a smile lit Casey&apos;s face.&lt;br/&gt;And when, responding to the cheers, he lightly doffed his hat,&lt;br/&gt;No stranger in the crowd could doubt &apos;twas Casey at the bat. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ten thousand eyes were on him as he rubbed his hands with dirt;&lt;br/&gt;Five thousand tongues applauded when he wiped them on his shirt;&lt;br/&gt;Then while the writhing pitcher ground the ball into his hip,&lt;br/&gt;Defiance flashed in Casey&apos;s eye, a sneer curled Casey&apos;s lip. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And now the leather-covered sphere came hurtling through the air,&lt;br/&gt;And Casey stood a-watching it in haughty grandeur there.&lt;br/&gt;Close by the sturdy batsman the ball unheeded sped-&lt;br/&gt;&apos;That ain&apos;t my style,&apos; said Casey. &apos;Strike one! &apos; the umpire said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From the benches, black with people, there went up a muffled roar,&lt;br/&gt;Like the beating of the storm-waves on a stern and distant shore;&lt;br/&gt;&apos;Kill him! Kill the umpire! &apos; shouted some one on the stand;&lt;br/&gt;And it&apos;s likely they&apos;d have killed him had not Casey raised his hand. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With a smile of Christian charity great Casey&apos;s visage shone;&lt;br/&gt;He stilled the rising tumult; he bade the game go on;&lt;br/&gt;He signaled to the pitcher, and once more the dun sphere flew;&lt;br/&gt;But Casey still ignored it, and the umpire said, &apos;Strike two! &apos; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&apos;Fraud! &apos; cried the maddened thousands, and echo answered &apos;Fraud! &apos;&lt;br/&gt;But one scornful look from Casey and the audience was awed.&lt;br/&gt;They saw his face grow stern and cold, they saw his muscles strain,&lt;br/&gt;And they knew that Casey wouldn&apos;t let that ball go by again. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The sneer has fled from Casey&apos;s lip, his teeth are clenched in hate;&lt;br/&gt;He pounds with cruel violence his bat upon the plate.&lt;br/&gt;And now the pitcher holds the ball, and now he lets it go.&lt;br/&gt;And now the air is shattered by the force of Casey&apos;s blow. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oh, somewhere in this favored land the sun is shining bright;&lt;br/&gt;The band is playing somewhere, and somewhere hearts are light,&lt;br/&gt;And somewhere men are laughing, and little children shout;&lt;br/&gt;But there is no joy in Mudville- mighty Casey has struck out. &amp;gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
	  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leap Second</title>
      <link>http://rmchale.github.io//blog/2015/leapsecond.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 3 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">blog/2015/leapsecond.html</guid>
      <description>
      &lt;p&gt;A while ago (okay June) I was up making sure our systems were okay during the leap second. I was hoping atleast to get a good example out of it using this fine script.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;sh&quot;&gt;while true; do date &amp;amp;&amp;amp; sleep 1; done
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sadly the mac has been fixed. Apparently over &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.jwz.org/blog/2005/12/happy-leap-second/&quot;&gt;10 years ago&lt;/a&gt;. Below I have output of the mac telling time correctly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;Tue Jun 30 18:59:52 CDT 2015
Tue Jun 30 18:59:53 CDT 2015
Tue Jun 30 18:59:54 CDT 2015
Tue Jun 30 18:59:55 CDT 2015
Tue Jun 30 18:59:56 CDT 2015
Tue Jun 30 18:59:57 CDT 2015
Tue Jun 30 18:59:58 CDT 2015
Tue Jun 30 18:59:59 CDT 2015
Tue Jun 30 19:00:00 CDT 2015
Tue Jun 30 19:00:01 CDT 2015
Tue Jun 30 19:00:02 CDT 2015
Tue Jun 30 19:00:03 CDT 2015
Tue Jun 30 19:00:04 CDT 2015
Tue Jun 30 19:00:05 CDT 2015
Tue Jun 30 19:00:06 CDT 2015
Tue Jun 30 19:00:07 CDT 2015
Tue Jun 30 19:00:08 CDT 2015
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
	  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>http://rmchale.github.io//blog/2014/12/first-post.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2014 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">blog/2014/12/first-post.html</guid>
      <description>
      This is my first blog post using jbake!

	  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second Post</title>
      <link>http://rmchale.github.io//blog/2014/12/second-post.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2014 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">blog/2014/12/second-post.html</guid>
      <description>
      This is my second blog post using jbake!

	  </description>
    </item>
    

  </channel> 
</rss>
